astromart.com 2006-10-18

# Astromart - Privacy Policy

Home > About Astromart > Privacy Policy

### Astromart Privacy Policy

This privacy statement discloses Astromart's information gathering and dissemination practices for the website [www.astromart.com](http://www.astromart.com/). 

Your browser transmits some information, such as your IP address, whenever you visit _any_ web site. Astromart uses this kind of information to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

If you respond to an ad, you enter your email address, but we do not store that email address; your reply goes only to the person who placed the ad. The ads themselves are stored in a secure SQL database. The only access to ad information is on the Astromart web site. 

Astromart's registration form requires users to provide contact information (like their name and email address) and your address. This information is used ONLY for Astromart ads. Your contact information is not and will not be sold or given to any third party or to Anacortes Telescope and Wild Bird, who provide Astromart as a free service to the amateur astronomy community. If required by any government authority, such as by subpoena, we will disclose information as required by law. 

This site contains links to other sites. Astromart is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Astromart receives ads from the general public. We use due diligence to remove ads that are not related to astronomy, that are inaccurate, and we may contact you if there is any question about your ad. Any information you post in your ad can be viewed by anyone who visits the site. 

We count the number of page hits on Astromart for various reasons, including the need to make sure we have enough hardware available to process the number of hits per day and per hour; to gauge whether Astromart is meeting the needs of its users, etc. We do not store any of your personal information whatsoever when we do this. 

#### Security 

Astromart has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Only you can make changes to, or delete your ad. Our administrative staff has the ability to remove ads that are not appropriate to the site, or to reduce the size of image files if they are too large for convenient viewing or overload the system. 

#### Email 

Astromart users have the option of receiving ads by email, either individually or in digest form. You have complete control over whether or not you receive email copies of ads; by default, no email whatsoever is sent to you. We do not send commercial email of any kind. Your email address is not sold or given to anyone for any reason. It is only used for the normal operation of Astromart, which is receiving and displaying classifieds ads for astronomy-related items. 

**To make any changes to your personal information on Astromart:**

You can visit the following URL once you log in:   
<http://www.astromart.com/myaccount/editaccount.asp>

You can send mail to the following postal address:  
9973 Padilla Heights Road  
Anacortes, Washington 98221 

To change the content of an ad you have placed, to change to change the expiration date of the ad, or to delete the ad, view the ad in the normal fashion and click the appropriate link. 

#### Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 

Astromart  
c/o Anacortes Telescope and Wild Bird  
9973 Padilla Heights Road  
Anacortes, Washington 98221  
360-588-9000
